donkparty.com 2018-09-06

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") applies to Shooshtime.com (the "Company"). As noted below, please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy in the future and it is your obligation to review this Privacy Policy from time to time and the effective date listed with it.

### ADULT ONLY SERVICE

_THIS IS AN ADULTS ONLY SERVICE._ We will terminate any accounts which we believe are being used by anyone under the age of eighteen (18) years old or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you view the Sites; additionally, we reserve the right to report such person to the proper authorities along with all information provided to us by or with respect to such person.

### DISCLOSURES MADE AS NECESSITATED BY LAW OR SAFETY

All information you provide u with is considered confidential. However, this information may be shared with other third parties as necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system.

### INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU

During your visit to shooshtime.com we may collect Demographic Information from you. Demographic Information may include IP address(es), referring website information, Internet browser used, zip code and/or other data regarding search history, browsing history, registration and user history.

### HOW IS THIS INFORMATION USED?

We may use Cookies and Demographic Information to better your experience on the site by allowing us to tailor your experience on the Sites according to your preferences and what we think may appeal to you based on such Demographic Information. Aggregate, non-individual membership Demographic Information may be shared with third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship who may offer products or services we believe you may be interested in.

We may also share the aggregate Demographic Information with third parties for the purposes of analyzing usage data, maintaining servers and other purposes relating to maintaining and improving our service and the Sites.

### YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO THIRD PARTIES

Any information provided by you to a third party, and any transaction with such a third party, is subject to that third party.s terms and conditions and privacy policy.

### EMAILS FROM US AND USE OF YOUR EMAIL ADDRESS

Your email address may be used by us to contact you when we have special offers or other information to provide you. Such information may include, without limitation, new services offered by us, information relating to your account and other information related to your subscription to the Sites. We may send you emails prior to and after you have terminated your membership to our service until such time as you advise us, in accordance with the procedures explained below, that you no longer wish to receive email from us and/or from third parties with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship. We may share your email address with other third parties, with whom we have a direct or indirect relationship with, for the purposes of sending you special advertisements or promotions. If at any time you no longer wish to receive emails from us or from such third parties please contact us at shoosh@shooshtime.com and request removal. We and our advertising partners fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act and as such all emails from us and our advertising partners will always, among other required disclosures, have a place for you to opt out of receipt of further email correspondence. Please note we will never send you an email directly or through our marketing partners without your consent. Please immediately report any emails you may receive, without your prior authorization, that purport to promote the Sites.

### ADVERTISEMENTS

We utilize the services of outside advertising agencies to advertise our services and goods and/or services offered by third parties. Either we or our advertising agencies may use cookies and/or action tags to measure advertising effectiveness on an anonymous basis. Some emails from us may contain advertisements from companies unrelated to the Sites. Should you elect to visit any such advertiser's website, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about applicable terms and conditions or privacy policies for such advertisers websites. If you choose to make any purchases on such sites or accept any offers from such companies, we may provide your information, including Financial Data, to the advertiser as necessary to your request. Finally, we cannot, and do not, make any representations about the privacy policies or terms and conditions of advertisements appearing anywhere on our service, whether through our website or emails, this is regardless of whether or not there may be any mentions of or references to any or all of the Sites on such advertiser's website(s).

### CHANGES OF PRIVACY POLICY

We may change this privacy policy at any time. You agree that we are under no duty to send you notice of such changes. Instead it is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy from time to time. No change in the privacy policy will be effective until thirty (30) days after it is posted, unless the privacy policy has clear language indicating otherwise.

### CHANGES IN THE OWNERSHIP OF THE SITE

Shooshtime.com is a growing online service. As such, we may have the occasion to buy or sell assets, including but not limited to merger, dissolution, and transfer of ownership. depending upon the nature of the transaction, we may share any and all data provided by you to us (including Financial Data and Account Information) with third parties, as necessary to initiate, investigate or complete any such transaction(s).

### CONTACT

Please address comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy to us via email to: shoosh(at)shooshtime.com.
